

Hugo MORCEAU

JavaScript Developer

► hugo.morceau@gmail.com
→ +33 6 58 02 10 65
← Sentmenat (Barcelona)

Profil

I'm a 33 years old french, cobol developer since 2012. I converted to web and mobile development in 2022. I am therefore looking for my first experience as a JS web developer, back and/or front and i'm especially interested in nodeJs / React / Vue / TypeScript.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer / Project Manager

2019 - 2022

Crédit Mutuel - Euro Information, Paris

Management of an international project

Writing functional and technical specifications in English

Conf call and emails in English

Supervision of developments and functional tests

Software Engineer

2017 - 2019

Equadra -> Crédit Mutuel - Euro Information, Paris

Developments in Cobol / Adélia / SQL

Software Engineer

2012 - 2016

Hardis Group, Paris

Services for various clients in the banking, insurance, factoring, and securitization sectors

Technical and functional analyses

Writing technical specifications

Workload estimates

Corrective and evolutive maintenance

Developments in Adélia IWS, Visual, CL, RPG, SQL

Unit tests, functional tests

Hotfixes in production

Writing documentation & user support

EDUCATION

Web and Mobile Web Developer

2022

O'Clock School

Information Systems Manager

2012 - 2013

CESI School, Châteauroux

Developer Analyst

2011 - 2012

CCI de l'indre, Châteauroux

Technical Skills

JavaScript, nodeJS, React

HTML, CSS

SQL (DB2, PSQL), Merise

Linux, AS400

Cobol, RPG4, Adélia IWS

Other skills

Project management

Writing specifications

Technical and functional analysis

Languages

French (native)

English - 910 on TOEIC

Spanish - B2

Links

Portfolio: hugomorceau.com

Linkedin.com/in/hugomorceau-5b36051b7/

Github.com/HugoMorceau